<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed>
   <job>
      <id><![CDATA[00010952-37e5-400c-a041-0f31824818bd]]></id>
        <title><![CDATA[Information Technology Procurement Manager]]></title>
        <contactName><![CDATA[Poundland &amp; Dealz]]></contactName>
        <companyDescription><![CDATA[<div><h2></h2><p><span>About the opportunity...<br></span><span><br></span><span>We are recruiting a Technology Procurement Manager to join the Procurement Team based at our Customer Support Centre in Walsall. The role has a flexible working location, allowing you to work from home and in the office.<br></span><span><br></span><span>Ensure you read the information regarding this opportunity thoroughly before making an application.<br></span><span><br></span><span>A key part of Poundland&amp;rsquo;s vision is to be &amp;ldquo;Technology Enabled&amp;rdquo;, so this is an important new role to the business. You will help Poundland and Dealz enable procurement of fit for purpose technology, manage spend, key suppliers, and service levels by guiding procurement processes and contract negotiations.<br></span><span><br></span><span>As a Technology Procurement Manager, you will report to the Head of Procurement. You will be the IT specialist within the team, working in partnership with the IT function to understand budgets and project plans for Poundland and Dealz. You will also work across other departments, playing a key role in projects that are enabled by technology.<br></span><span><br></span><span>We are committed to supporting our colleagues with their development, this role comes with the ability to study an apprenticeship in Commercial Procurement and supply level 4 or Supply Chain Leadership Professional (Integrated Degree) Level 6<br></span></p></div><div><h2>What you will be doing&amp;hellip;</h2><ul><li>﻿</li></ul></div><div><h2>As the Technology Procurement Manager, your duties will include</h2><ul><li>Identify opportunities to generate efficiencies and improve cost</li><li>To lead on the end-to-end procurement and vendor management for the IT department</li><li>To lead and manage RFPs (Request for Proposals) with new and existing suppliers</li><li>To act as the principal conduit for formal communications with external companies during the procurement process and participate directly in the negotiation of key contracts to obtain the best outcome possible for Poundland</li><li>To work with Contract owners to assist with all commercial matters, educate and coach others to improve buying practices</li><li>To proactively manage relationships with senior stakeholders to deliver outstanding commercial outcomes</li><li>To play an active role in the company's Sustainability plan to include ethical and responsible sourcing</li></ul></div><div><h2>What you'll need..</h2><ul><li>At least five years of experience in managing IT procurement in a fast-paced environment (Retail or FMCG)</li><li>Commercial negotiation and supplier management experience with a track record delivering cost savings, service improvements, and supplier innovation</li><li>Proven stakeholder influencing skills and experience in supplier development and commercial cost reduction</li><li>Practical knowledge of IT service agreements, Licensing and SAAS agreements</li><li>Excellent presentation and influencing skills</li><li>Substantial time and project management skills</li><li>Working towards, or MCIPS qualified (Member of the Chartered Institute of Procurement and Supply)</li></ul></div>]]></companyDescription>
        <jobDescription><![CDATA[EntrepriseSuperprof est  l'outil de partage de connaissances par excellence. Il met en relation ceux qui désirent apprendre et ceux qui souhaitent enseigner.

          Créée en août 2013, Superprof connecte des élèves et des professeurs pour des leçons sur plus de 1000 disciplines: musique (guitare, piano, etc.), langues, sports (golf, coach sportif, natation, etc.) et matières scolaires (maths, français, philo, etc.).

          Huit millions d’utilisateurs se sont servis de cette plateforme en 2019, majoritairement en France mais aussi dans 36 autres pays (https://www.superprof.fr/superprof-dans-le-monde.html)MissionLeader en Europe sur la mise en relation d’élèves et professeurs particuliers , Superprof recherche des intervenants pédagogiques toute l'année dans toute la Suisse pour dispenser des cours particuliers dans de nombreux domaines : matières scolaires, langues, musique, chant, sports, loisirs…

          En fonction de vos connaissances et expériences, vous pouvez proposer des cours et créer autant d'annonces que vous voulez.  Rejoignez l’équipe de Superprof directement en cliquant ici et donnez des cours privés à des élèves proche de chez vous, de tout niveau et de tout âge.

          95% des professeurs inscrits trouvent plus d’élèves sur Superprof que sur n’importe quelle autre plateforme.

          Profil :
          -Vous êtes titulaire d'un diplôme de niveau bac minimum (ou équivalent)
          -Vous souhaitez transmettre votre savoir, votre passion et vos connaissances à des élèves
          -Vous êtes patient, ponctuel et pédagogueAvantages-Inscription totalement gratuite
          -Une rémunération attractive, nette et sans surprise (pas de commission)
          -      Paiement via Superprof
          -      Mise en place d'une politique d'annulation
          -Une maîtrise de votre emploi du temps
          -Une multitude d’élèves : plus de 100 000 recherches / jour
          -La possibilité de donner des cours via webcam]]></jobDescription>

      <location><![CDATA[Bangalore, Karnataka, India]]></location>
      <workingTimes><![CDATA[Full Time]]></workingTimes>
         <category><![CDATA[Quality Engineer]]></category>
         <skills><![CDATA[Computers - PowerPoint,Computers - Excel,Computers - Word]]></skills>
        <designation><![CDATA[Python Developer]]></designation>
        <experience><![CDATA[15-35]]></experience>
        <salary><![CDATA[30000-1000000]]></salary>
        <keywords><![CDATA[call, customer]]></keywords>
        <contact_number><![CDATA[9787800000]]></contact_number>
        <company_website><![CDATA[https://www.google.com]]></company_website>
        <last_date><![CDATA[2021-09-09]]></last_date>

    </job>

    <job>
        <id><![CDATA[12345678-abcd-1234-efgh-87654321dcba]]></id>
        <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer]]></title>
        <contactName><![CDATA[Tech Solutions Inc.]]></contactName>
        <companyDescription><![CDATA[<div><h2></h2><p><span>About the opportunity...<br></span><span><br></span><span>We are looking for a Senior Software Engineer to join our dynamic team. This role is based in our office in Silicon Valley, but we offer flexible working arrangements.<br></span><span><br></span><span>As a Senior Software Engineer, you will be responsible for designing and developing cutting-edge software solutions. You will collaborate with cross-functional teams and lead projects to success.<br></span><span><br></span><span>Join us to work on exciting projects and advance your career in the tech industry.<br></span></p></div>]]></companyDescription>
        <jobDescription><![CDATA[Superprof is the leading platform for knowledge sharing. It connects learners with teachers across a wide range of subjects and disciplines.

          Founded in 2013, Superprof facilitates lessons in over 1,000 areas, including music (guitar, piano, etc.), languages, sports (golf, personal training, swimming, etc.), and academic subjects (math, French, philosophy, etc.).

          In 2019, over 8 million users used our platform, predominantly in France but also in 36 other countries (https://www.superprof.fr/superprof-dans-le-monde.html).

          Mission:
          As the leader in Europe for connecting students and private tutors, Superprof is continuously seeking educational professionals in Switzerland to provide private lessons in various fields, including academic subjects, languages, music, singing, sports, and leisure activities.

          Depending on your knowledge and experience, you can offer lessons and create as many listings as you'd like. Join the Superprof team by clicking here and teach private lessons to students in your area, regardless of their level or age.

          95% of registered tutors find more students on Superprof than on any other platform.

          Profile:
          - You have at least a high school diploma (or equivalent).
          - You want to share your knowledge, passion, and expertise with students.
          - You are patient, punctual, and a good teacher.

          Benefits:
          - Completely free registration
          - Competitive, commission-free compensation
          - Payment through Superprof
          - Implementation of a cancellation policy
          - Control over your schedule
          - Access to a large pool of students: over 100,000 daily searches
          - The opportunity to teach lessons via webcam]]></jobDescription>
        <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, California, USA]]></location>
        <workingTimes><![CDATA[Full Time]]></workingTimes>
        <category><![CDATA[Design Engineer]]></category>
        <skills><![CDATA[Java, Python, SQL]]></skills>
        <designation><![CDATA[Python Developer]]></designation>
        <experience><![CDATA[1-2]]></experience>
        <salary><![CDATA[5000-7000]]></salary>
        <keywords><![CDATA[programming, software development]]></keywords>
        <contact_number><![CDATA[123-456-7890]]></contact_number>
        <company_website><![CDATA[https://www.techsolutionsinc.com]]></company_website>
        <last_date><![CDATA[2023-12-31]]></last_date>
    </job>

    <job>
        <id><![CDATA[456789ab-1234-5678-cdef-9876543210dc]]></id>
        <title><![CDATA[Network Security Analyst]]></title>
        <contactName><![CDATA[TechGuard Solutions]]></contactName>
        <companyDescription><![CDATA[<div><h2></h2><p><span>About the opportunity...<br></span><span><br></span><span>We are seeking a Network Security Analyst to join our cybersecurity team based at our headquarters in San Francisco. This role offers both in-office and remote work options.<br></span><span><br></span><span>Before applying, please carefully review the details of this opportunity.<br></span><span><br></span><span>At TechGuard Solutions, our mission is to ensure the security and integrity of our clients' networks and systems. As a Network Security Analyst, you will play a crucial role in safeguarding our clients' digital assets by monitoring for threats, implementing security measures, and responding to incidents.<br></span><span><br></span><span>You will report to the Head of Cybersecurity and collaborate with IT teams to maintain a secure and resilient network environment. Join us in our mission to protect digital infrastructure from cyber threats.<br></span></p></div>]]></companyDescription>
        <jobDescription><![CDATA[Superprof is the premier platform for knowledge sharing. It connects individuals seeking to learn with those wishing to teach.

          Established in August 2013, Superprof facilitates lessons in over 1,000 disciplines, including music (guitar, piano, etc.), languages, sports (golf, personal training, swimming, etc.), and academic subjects (math, French, philosophy, etc.).

          In 2019, more than 8 million users utilized our platform, primarily in France, but also in 36 other countries (https://www.superprof.fr/superprof-dans-le-monde.html).

          Mission:
          As the leading platform in Europe for connecting students and private tutors, Superprof is continually searching for educational professionals in Switzerland to offer private lessons in a wide range of subjects, including academic subjects, languages, music, singing, sports, and leisure activities.

          Depending on your expertise and experience, you can provide lessons and create as many listings as you desire. Join the Superprof team by clicking here and offer private lessons to students in your vicinity, regardless of their age or level.

          95% of registered tutors find more students on Superprof than on any other platform.

          Profile:
          - You hold at least a high school diploma (or its equivalent).
          - You want to share your knowledge, passion, and expertise with students.
          - You are patient, punctual, and a good teacher.

          Benefits:
          - Registration is completely free.
          - Competitive, commission-free compensation.
          - Payment through Superprof.
          - Implementation of a cancellation policy.
          - Control over your schedule.
          - Access to a large pool of students: over 100,000 daily searches.
          - The ability to provide lessons via webcam]]></jobDescription>
        <location><![CDATA[London, United Kingdom]]></location>
        <workingTimes><![CDATA[Seasonal]]></workingTimes>
        <category><![CDATA[Engineering]]></category>
        <skills><![CDATA[PeopleSoft, Oracle, Developer]]></skills>
        <designation><![CDATA[Python Developer]]></designation>
        <experience><![CDATA[2-5]]></experience>
        <salary><![CDATA[10000-12000]]></salary>
        <keywords><![CDATA[security, network monitoring]]></keywords>
        <contact_number><![CDATA[555-123-4567]]></contact_number>
        <company_website><![CDATA[https://www.techguardsolutions.com]]></company_website>
        <last_date><![CDATA[2023-11-30]]></last_date>
    </job>
<job>
    <id><![CDATA[1a2b3c4d-5678-9abc-def0-1234e5f6gh78]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Development Manager]]></title>
    <contactName><![CDATA[Tech Innovators Inc.]]></contactName>
    <companyDescription><![CDATA[<div><h2></h2><p><span>About the opportunity...<br></span><span><br></span><span>We're looking for a Software Development Manager to lead our innovative team. This position can be remote or based at our headquarters in San Jose, California.<br></span><span><br></span><span>Please review the details of this opportunity before applying.<br></span><span><br></span><span>At Tech Innovators, we are committed to pushing the boundaries of technology. As a Software Development Manager, you will play a crucial role in driving innovation, managing development projects, and leading a dynamic team of software engineers.<br></span><span><br></span><span>You'll report to the Head of Development and collaborate with cross-functional teams to create cutting-edge solutions.<br></span></p></div>]]></companyDescription>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[Superprof is the ultimate platform for sharing knowledge. It connects learners with teachers in over 1,000 subjects, including music (guitar, piano, etc.), languages, sports (golf, personal training, swimming, etc.), and academic subjects (math, French, philosophy, etc.).

      Established in August 2013, Superprof facilitates lessons for millions of users worldwide, with a strong presence in France and 36 other countries (https://www.superprof.fr/superprof-dans-le-monde.html).

      Mission:
      As the leader in connecting students with private tutors in Europe, Superprof is constantly seeking educators in Switzerland to offer private lessons in various subjects, including academic, language, music, sports, and more.

      Depending on your expertise, you can create listings and provide lessons in your area. Join the Superprof team to teach students of all levels and ages.

      95% of our registered tutors find more students on Superprof than on any other platform.

      Profile:
      - Minimum of a high school diploma or equivalent.
      - Desire to share knowledge and passion with students.
      - Patience, punctuality, and teaching skills.

      Benefits:
      - Free registration.
      - Competitive, commission-free compensation.
      - Payment through Superprof.
      - Cancellation policy.
      - Flexible scheduling.
      - Access to a large pool of students: over 100,000 daily searches.
      - Ability to give lessons via webcam]]></jobDescription>
    <location><![CDATA[San Jose, California, USA]]></location>
    <workingTimes><![CDATA[Seasonal]]></workingTimes>
    <category><![CDATA[Biotech]]></category>
    <skills><![CDATA[Manufacturing, Agile Digital Marketing Specialist]]></skills>
    <designation><![CDATA[Mechanic - All]]></designation>
    <experience><![CDATA[1-2]]></experience>
    <salary><![CDATA[10000-120000]]></salary>
    <keywords><![CDATA[innovation, team leadership]]></keywords>
    <contact_number><![CDATA[408-123-4567]]></contact_number>
    <company_website><![CDATA[https://www.techinnovators.com]]></company_website>
    <last_date><![CDATA[2023-12-31]]></last_date>
</job>
<job>
    <id><![CDATA[abcdef12-3456-7890-cdef-1234abcd5678]]></id>
    <title><![CDATA[Frontend Developer]]></title>
    <contactName><![CDATA[WebTech Solutions]]></contactName>
    <companyDescription><![CDATA[<div><h2></h2><p><span>About the opportunity...<br></span><span><br></span><span>We're seeking a Frontend Developer to join our talented web development team. This role offers flexibility in work location, allowing remote or office-based work.<br></span><span><br></span><span>Please review the job details before applying.<br></span><span><br></span><span>At WebTech Solutions, we are dedicated to creating user-friendly web applications. As a Frontend Developer, you'll be responsible for designing and implementing engaging user interfaces, collaborating with backend developers, and ensuring optimal user experiences.<br></span><span><br></span><span>You'll report to the Head of Web Development and participate in shaping our web technology vision.<br></span></p></div>]]></companyDescription>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[Superprof is the go-to platform for knowledge exchange, connecting individuals who want to learn with those who wish to teach.

      Founded in August 2013, Superprof facilitates lessons in over 1,000 disciplines, including music (guitar, piano, etc.), languages, sports (golf, personal training, swimming, etc.), and academic subjects (math, French, philosophy, etc.).

      In 2019, over 8 million users utilized our platform, with a strong presence in France and 36 other countries (https://www.superprof.fr/superprof-dans-le-monde.html).

      Mission:
      As the leading platform in Europe for connecting students and private tutors, Superprof is continually seeking educational professionals in Switzerland to offer private lessons in a wide range of subjects, including academic subjects, languages, music, sports, and leisure activities.

      Depending on your knowledge and experience, you can provide lessons and create as many listings as you desire. Join the Superprof team to offer private lessons to students of all ages and levels.

      95% of registered tutors find more students on Superprof than on any other platform.

      Profile:
      - You hold at least a high school diploma (or equivalent).
      - You want to share your knowledge, passion, and expertise with students.
      - You are patient, punctual, and a good teacher.

      Benefits:
      - Registration is completely free.
      - Competitive, commission-free compensation.
      - Payment through Superprof.
      - Implementation of a cancellation policy.
      - Control over your schedule.
      - Access to a large pool of students: over 100,000 daily searches.
      - The possibility to provide lessons via webcam]]></jobDescription>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York, USA]]></location>
    <workingTimes><![CDATA[Full Time]]></workingTimes>
    <category><![CDATA[Process Engineer]]></category>
    <skills><![CDATA[iPad/Tablet, Customer Service, Computers - PowerPoint, Computers - Apple]]></skills>
    <designation><![CDATA[Python Developer]]></designation>
    <experience><![CDATA[5-7]]></experience>
    <salary><![CDATA[20000-25000]]></salary>
    <keywords><![CDATA[frontend, user interfaces]]></keywords>
    <contact_number><![CDATA[212-555-1234]]></contact_number>
    <company_website><![CDATA[https://www.webtechsolutions.com]]></company_website>
    <last_date><![CDATA[2023-11-30]]></last_date>
</job>


</feed>